Hello to you, I have something else and you are listening to me
on Fact Junction, so friends,
a press release from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs
and they informed that there is
no need to call Bigg Boss
because they have bought it and if we
talk about it, then you will get total subscription to quote for
25 years.
If we talk about these numbers in the market from ICICI Lombard, then
this general insurance company has
registered itself here
and these product details are from a separate
distribution company, joint venture
company General Motors Private Limited,
management company Global Management Company,
one percent shares of this company are going to be
in the general stores of both the companies, that means the general
insurance company will be released on Bharti Airtel
and it will be combined with ICICI Lombard.
If you talk about these numbers, then
they have done good business in the last year.
If you talk about good numbers, then
they have maintained a report of Rs 2833 crore in a week.
ICICI Lombard has earned an income of Rs 2883 crore.
If we talk about quarterly bumper, then
ICICI  Lombard has made a
computer of Rs 415 crore, its
manufacturing has started, now General Insurance
is going to acquire it, they have got it from the Competition Commission, the
Competition Commission of India,
they have
approved it under Section 311 of the Competition Act of August 2002, so
what is your opinion about this,
please tell us in the comment section or take care of yourself,
if you go out for work then
you must sanitize yourself, take
care, have a nice day